And what I kind of noticed is that everybody in your team kind of looks the same. So we're
going to have to switch it up. Okay. Now I understand that your team is under a lot of
pressure to deliver and that I know you all are different. I do. But you know, Shay, the only
person on your team has kind of been reaching out to us and saying, Hey, there's not much diversity
here. And you know, I'm trying to get her to understand that there's more like diversity and
thought, but we may have to switch it up just a little bit. So let me just share my screen.
Okay, so first things first, we're going to have to encourage Shay to keep that camera on. Okay.
Now, here are some suggestions that I have considering that maybe some of you can kind
of like maybe pick a person to go brunette, you know, like, you know, draw straws and say,
Okay, you're gonna go you're gonna be a redhead. Okay, kind of switch it up a little bit. Maybe we
can add, you know, a couple of more glasses and the mix maybe some more like deep sight parts. Okay,
I kind of like switch it up a little bit. And that's just to make sure that we're kind
of following up on the inclusive practices that we have where we acknowledge all different
types of diversity. Okay. Now your diversity lies on the inside of you. We want to kind
of draw it out of you. Okay. Now maybe it's time for one of you to procure a contractor
to maybe say paint a wall behind you. So you know, maybe we can find some different color
variations there where like, Hey, so and so has a blue wall. So it has a purple wall, you
know, because it's just kind of all looking kind of like the same shade all around. Okay.
Now as much as we love having octuplets run a team here, you know, it might be time to
kind of like break up the band. Okay. I know you guys kind of all did this group interview
together and said, Hey, we're we're all eight people that were born at the same time. And
we like to work together. I get it. But it may be time to kind of like place you in other
departments. And that's going to be for your benefit. Okay.
Okay.
So
you